<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mobile on Blog Coderockr</title>
    <link>https://blog.coderockr.com/tags/mobile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mobile on Blog Coderockr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>pt-br</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.coderockr.com/tags/mobile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Android x iOS: 6 Pontos Essenciais no Desenvolvimento de Aplicativos</title>
      <link>https://blog.coderockr.com/posts/2018/android-x-ios-6-pontos-essenciais-no-desenvolvimento-de-aplicativos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.coderockr.com/posts/2018/android-x-ios-6-pontos-essenciais-no-desenvolvimento-de-aplicativos/</guid>
      <description>O mercado de aplicativos para celulares é um dos mais rentáveis, a maioria das empresas já entendeu que é fundamental ter um bom produto mobile para atender cada vez melhor seus clientes. Isso significa que a demanda por mão de obra qualificada é crescente, como também a busca por uma fábrica de software, que se compromete a longo prazo com o sucesso do seu produto, desde sua criação a manutenção dele, com todas as melhorias e inovações.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>React Native for React Developers</title>
      <link>https://blog.coderockr.com/posts/2017/react-native-for-react-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.coderockr.com/posts/2017/react-native-for-react-developers/</guid>
      <description>React Native for React Developers
React Native is becoming the definitive solution to create apps across multiple platforms. What React Native offers, is the possibility to create native mobile apps using only Javascript.
In this post, I am going to make a comparison between React and React Native, and what are the first things a React Developer should know before starting to code.
Building Blocks React Native uses the same design as React, you will be using JSX and JavaScript to create your components.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>